光看着马的眼睛
You can't look in a horse's eyes
是看不出个所以然的
and tell there's something wrong.
你甚至无法同时看着马的两只眼睛
You can't even look in their eyes at the same time --
不在一边啊
One's here and one's here!
走吧  我们去窗口领钱
Come on. Let's go to the window, kid.
我一个人可拿不动那么多
I may need some help carrying my winnings.
且慢
Oh. Wait.
杰  你看
Jay, look.
[调查中]
调查中
Inquiry.
那是什么意思
What's that?
就是有匹马违规了
It is when a horse has committed an infraction.
可能违规  通常没什么大碍
Possible infraction. Usually it's nothing.
我确定
I'm sure...
九号马"小培根"
The number 9 horse little bacon
由于"非法阻挡"被取消冠军资格
has been disqualified for interference.
搞什么
What?!
冠军是6号马  "布拉德的蜡光皮衣"
The winner is number 6 bradswaxjacket.
瞧见没
You see?